eamega.com 2013-05-02

# Privacy Policy

**Online Privacy Statement**

It is Amega Global LLC / Amega Global Ltd’s (henceforth referred to as Amega) policy to respect our customers' right to privacy online. Amega Global hold your detailed customer information in confidence.

 **Asking for your information**

Amega Global will sometimes ask customers for personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address, and other details. Providing us your information is solely for the purposes of shipping your products or informing you of the latest offers you may be interested in. When you choose to give personal information to us over the Internet that Amega Global may request, Amega Global will endeavor to inform you how this information will be used.

When Amega Global asks for personal information for any reason, we will provide a link to this policy statement to make our intentions clear.

 **Personal Information Privacy**

Amega Global will take all appropriate steps to keep your personal information confidential. Those steps include limiting access to customer information databases, communicating this policy statement to all our employees and establishing and enforcing penalties for violating this statement.

Amega Global will not sell, rent, or give away our customers' personal information to other companies for use in selling others' products or services. When Amega Global do contract with another company to market or advertise products or services for us, Amega Global will insist on binding agreements from those companies protecting our customer information. Amega Global will vigorously enforce all privacy agreements Amega Global have with other companies.

Amega Global will communicate with customers via e-mail or other online delivery devices only if the customer agrees to receive those communications. Customers, who believe they are receiving our communications in error or no longer desire to receive them, should inform us and Amega Global will remove those customers' names from our mailing lists. Amega Global will be judicious in the use of e-mail and paper mail to communicate with customers. Amega Global will, at all times, put ourselves in the place of the recipients of our mail and treat our customers as Amega Global ourselves would like to be treated.
